<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1Album</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 1Album</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Completely Free</title>
      <link>/cost/cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cost/cost/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 class=&#34;quotation&#34;&gt;
&#34;My phone is almost full.  I need to move my photos off the phone.&#34;
&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&#34;quotation&#34;&gt;
&#34;I want to keep my photos forever, but not paying someone forever to keep them.&#34;
&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 class=&#34;quotation&#34;&gt;
&#34;I want to easily view all my photos even when they are off my phone.&#34;
&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;
1Album achieves all of the above, and is absolutely free.  
&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;!--
    1Album backs up full size photos and videos on your phone to your computer then cleans up space from your phone.  After that, you still have access to all the photos and videos, which are served directly from your computer through a secured peer-to-peer network connection to your phone.

--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faster</title>
      <link>/features/1faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/1faster/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With peer-to-peer connections link directly from your phone to your computer, you can enjoy the maxium network bandwith available between them for backing up photos and videos.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup 1Album Blackbox on your computer</title>
      <link>/steps/step1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/steps/step1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1Album Blackbox is the storage backend for 1Album.  It can be installed on Windows, Mac OSX, Linux, NAS devices, and many other environments that can run a Docker container.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheaper</title>
      <link>/features/2cheaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/2cheaper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Backing up any amount of full size photos and videos is absolutely free of charge.  Our business is supported by displaying limited amount of Ads in 1Album app. You can pay a small monthly fee to make the Ads go away, but this is completely optional.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sign in to 1Album from your phone</title>
      <link>/steps/step2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/steps/step2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Install 1Album app on your iPhone or iPad and sign in with your Facebook account. Other sign in methods are comming.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Link 1Album Blackbox to your account</title>
      <link>/steps/step3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/steps/step3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Link 1Album Blackbox to your account by entering your blackbox&amp;rsquo;s device code in 1Album app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Private</title>
      <link>/features/3private/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/3private/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Your photos and videos are stored privately in your phone or your computer. 1Album and 1Album Blackbox communicate through encrypted direct peer-to-peer channels without tunneling through any servers or strangers.  So only you have access to your photos and videos. They never send to us or anyone else.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Size Backup</title>
      <link>/features/4fullsize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/4fullsize/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1Album backup full size photos and videos to 1Album Blackbox, so you won&amp;rsquo;t loose any details in your photos. Live photos are also supported.  If a photo have been edited on iPhone, both edited version and the unedited one are backed up.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s it!</title>
      <link>/steps/step4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/steps/step4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Now 1Album app will back up photos and videos on your phone to your 1Album Blackbox automatically. You can delete some or all of the backed up items from your phone to free up space, and you still have access to all of the items from 1Album app through a secured peer-to-peer connection links directly to your 1Album Blackbox.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works Offline</title>
      <link>/features/5offline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/5offline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When offline, you can still make changes in 1Album or view photos and videos that are already stored on your phone.  All the changes you made will synchronize back to 1Album Blackbox when you are online.  Likewise, you can setup 1Album Blackbox on a laptop and turn it on only when you need it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fail Safe</title>
      <link>/features/6failsafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/6failsafe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You can add multiple 1Album Blackboxes to your account, and they will synchronize with each other automatically. To be even safer, you can put them in different physical locations.  You will not loose your data should any one of them fail.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy to Setup</title>
      <link>/features/7easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/7easy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1Album and 1Album Blackbox do not need any special network setup to connect. Our UDP-based peer-to-peer connection can go through most NAT routers.  If your computer can browse the Internet, 1Album can connect to 1Album Blackbox installed on your computer. It&amp;rsquo;s that easy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works without Blackboxes</title>
      <link>/features/8nobox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/features/8nobox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t have 1Album Blackbox set up, you can still use 1Album from your iPad to view photos and videos on your iPhone, and vise versa.  Powered by the same peer-to-peer technology, 1Album gives you a single album view to all photos and videos scattered around your devices, hence the name &amp;ldquo;1Album&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>