<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Features on 1Album</title>
    <link>/en/features/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Features on 1Album</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="/en/features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Faster</title>
      <link>/en/features/1faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/1faster/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Backing up photos is very fast with peer-to-peer connections link directly from your phone to your blackbox. It is especially so when they are in the same local network.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheaper</title>
      <link>/en/features/2cheaper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/2cheaper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Storing any amount of full size photos and videos with 1Album is absolutely free, as opposed to most cloud services which charge you by the amount of data you have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our business is supported by displaying limited amount of Ads in 1Album app. You can pay a small monthly fee to make the Ads go away, but this is completely optional.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Private</title>
      <link>/en/features/3private/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/3private/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The communication channels between 1Album app and 1Album Blackbox are end-to-end encrypted.  Your data never travel through the Internet unencrypted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your photos and videos are never sent to cloud services or strangers&amp;rsquo; computers either.  They are stored only on the devices that you own. Nobody else has access to them.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Size Photos</title>
      <link>/en/features/4fullsize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/4fullsize/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1Album app stores full size photos and videos in 1Album Blackbox, so you won&amp;rsquo;t loose any details in your photos. Live Photos are also supported.  If a photo have been edited on iPhone, both the edited and the original versions are stored.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy to Setup</title>
      <link>/en/features/5easy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/5easy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1Album peer-to-peer connections can pass through most NAT routers and cellular networks without special configurations. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to fiddle with port mapping or UPnP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If your computer can browse the web, 1Album app can connect to 1Album Blackbox on that computer. It&amp;rsquo;s that easy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fail Safe</title>
      <link>/en/features/6failsafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/6failsafe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you add multiple 1Album Blackboxes to your account, they will synchronize with each other automatically. Each blackbox has full copy of all your data, so you won&amp;rsquo;t loose precious photos should any one of them fail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can even put blackboxes at locations far apart from each other to protect your data from natural disasters.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works Offline</title>
      <link>/en/features/7offline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/7offline/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Other than downloading photos that are not currently on the phone, you can do almost everything with 1Album app offline, from posting comments to organizing photos. Changes you made will synchronize back to 1Album Blackbox once it is reachable again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result, you can install 1Album Blackbox on a laptop and turn the blackbox on only when you need it.  It does not need to run 24x7.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App-to-app Access</title>
      <link>/en/features/8nobox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/features/8nobox/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;rsquo;t set up any blackboxes or can&amp;rsquo;t connect to one at the moment, 1Album app on your iPhone and iPad can talk to each other directly as long as there is network between them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can view photos on your iPhone from an iPad, and vise versa. Organizing photos on one device is synchronized to the other device immediately.  This even works with more than two devices. It&amp;rsquo;s just like magic.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>