<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supports on 1Album</title>
    <link>http://1album.net/tw/support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supports on 1Album</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <atom:link href="http://1album.net/tw/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://1album.net/tw/support/_menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1album.net/tw/support/_menu/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://1album.net/tw/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1album.net/tw/support/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;服務&#34;&gt;服務&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;我要如何停止訂閱移除廣告&#34;&gt;我要如何停止訂閱移除廣告？&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;取消訂閱必須透過 Apple 的 iTunes 與 App Store 來操作。請參考 &lt;a href=&#34;https://support.apple.com/zh-tw/HT202039&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;檢視、更改或取消訂閱&lt;/a&gt; 內有詳細步驟。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://1album.net/tw/support/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1album.net/tw/support/terms/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;服務條款&#34;&gt;服務條款&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please read these Terms and Conditions (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Terms and Conditions&amp;rdquo;) carefully before using the &lt;a href=&#34;http://1album.net&#34;&gt;http://1album.net&lt;/a&gt; website, the 1Album mobile application, and the 1Album Blackbox application (the &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;) operated by 1 Digital Inc. (&amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;).
Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users and others who access or use the Service.
By accessing or using the Service you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms then you may not access the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;subscriptions&#34;&gt;Subscriptions&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some parts of the Service are billed on a subscription basis (&amp;ldquo;Subscription(s)&amp;rdquo;). You will be billed in advance on a recurring and periodic basis (&amp;ldquo;Billing Cycle&amp;rdquo;). Billing cycles are set on a monthly basis.
At the end of each Billing Cycle, your Subscription will automatically renew under the exact same conditions unless you cancel it or 1 Digital Inc. cancels it. You may cancel your Subscription renewal either through your online account management page or by contacting 1 Digital Inc. customer support team.
A valid payment method, including credit card, is required to process the payment for your Subscription. You shall provide 1 Digital Inc. with accurate and complete billing information including full name, address, state, zip code, telephone number, and a valid payment method information. By submitting such payment information, you automatically authorize 1 Digital Inc. to charge all Subscription fees incurred through your account to any such payment instruments.
Should automatic billing fail to occur for any reason, 1 Digital Inc. will issue an electronic invoice indicating that you must proceed manually, within a certain deadline date, with the full payment corresponding to the billing period as indicated on the invoice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;fee-changes&#34;&gt;Fee Changes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 Digital Inc., in its sole discretion and at any time, may modify the Subscription fees for the Subscriptions. Any Subscription fee change will become effective at the end of the then-current Billing Cycle.
1 Digital Inc. will provide you with a reasonable prior notice of any change in Subscription fees to give you an opportunity to terminate your Subscription before such change becomes effective.
Your continued use of the Service after the Subscription fee change comes into effect constitutes your agreement to pay the modified Subscription fee amount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;refunds&#34;&gt;Refunds&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Except when required by law, paid Subscription fees are non-refundable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;content&#34;&gt;Content&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Service allows you to post, link, store, share and otherwise make available certain information, text, graphics, videos, or other material (&amp;ldquo;Content&amp;rdquo;). You are responsible for the Content that you post to the Service, including its legality, reliability, and appropriateness.
By posting Content to the Service, you grant us the right and license to use, modify, publicly perform, publicly display, reproduce, and distribute such Content on and through the Service. You retain any and all of your rights to any Content you submit, post or display on or through the Service and you are responsible for protecting those rights.
You represent and warrant that: (i) the Content is yours (you own it) or you have the right to use it and grant us the rights and license as provided in these Terms, and (ii) the posting of your Content on or through the Service does not violate the privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, contract rights or any other rights of any person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;accounts&#34;&gt;Accounts&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you create an account with us, you must provide us information that is accurate, complete, and current at all times. Failure to do so constitutes a breach of the Terms, which may result in immediate termination of your account on our Service.
You are responsible for safeguarding the password that you use to access the Service and for any activities or actions under your password, whether your password is with our Service or a third-party service.
You agree not to disclose your password to any third party. You must notify us immediately upon becoming aware of any breach of security or unauthorized use of your account.
You may not use as a username the name of another person or entity or that is not lawfully available for use, a name or trade mark that is subject to any rights of another person or entity other than you without appropriate authorization, or a name that is otherwise offensive, vulgar or obscene.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;intellectual-property&#34;&gt;Intellectual Property&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Service and its original content (excluding Content provided by users), features and functionality are and will remain the exclusive property of 1 Digital Inc. and its licensors. The Service is protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the Taiwan and foreign countries. Our trademarks and trade dress may not be used in connection with any product or service without the prior written consent of 1 Digital Inc..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;links-to-other-web-sites&#34;&gt;Links To Other Web Sites&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Service may contain links to third-party web sites or services that are not owned or controlled by 1 Digital Inc..
1 Digital Inc. has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that 1 Digital Inc. shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services available on or through any such web sites or services.
We strongly advise you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policies of any third-party web sites or services that you visit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;termination&#34;&gt;Termination&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may terminate or suspend your account immediately, without prior notice or liability, for any reason whatsoever, including without limitation if you breach the Terms.
Upon termination, your right to use the Service will immediately cease. If you wish to terminate your account, you may simply discontinue using the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;limitation-of-liability&#34;&gt;Limitation Of Liability&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In no event shall 1 Digital Inc., nor its directors, employees, partners, agents, suppliers, or affiliates, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages, including without limitation, loss of profits, data, use, goodwill, or other intangible losses, resulting from (i) your access to or use of or inability to access or use the Service; (ii) any conduct or content of any third party on the Service; (iii) any content obtained from the Service; and (iv) unauthorized access, use or alteration of your transmissions or content, whether based on warranty, contract, tort (including negligence) or any other legal theory, whether or not we have been informed of the possibility of such damage, and even if a remedy set forth herein is found to have failed of its essential purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;disclaimer&#34;&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your use of the Service is at your sole risk. The Service is provided on an &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;AS AVAILABLE&amp;rdquo; basis. The Service is provided without warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement or course of performance.
1 Digital Inc. its subsidiaries, affiliates, and its licensors do not warrant that a) the Service will function uninterrupted, secure or available at any particular time or location; b) any errors or defects will be corrected; c) the Service is free of viruses or other harmful components; or d) the results of using the Service will meet your requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;governing-law&#34;&gt;Governing Law&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These Terms shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of Taiwan, without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
Our failure to enforce any right or provision of these Terms will not be considered a waiver of those rights. If any provision of these Terms is held to be invalid or unenforceable by a court, the remaining provisions of these Terms will remain in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us regarding our Service, and supersede and replace any prior agreements we might have between us regarding the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;changes&#34;&gt;Changes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. If a revision is material we will try to provide at least 30 days notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.
By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:service@1album.net&#34;&gt;service@1album.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1 Digital Inc.&lt;br&gt;
4F-1, No.48, Sec.2, Keelung Rd., Taipei 110, Taiwan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&#34;pull-right&#34;&gt;Last updated: June 15, 2016&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://1album.net/tw/support/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1album.net/tw/support/privacy/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;隱私權政策&#34;&gt;隱私權政策&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 Digital Inc. (&amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) operates the &lt;a href=&#34;http://1album.net&#34;&gt;http://1album.net&lt;/a&gt; website, the 1Album mobile application, and the 1Album Blackbox application (the &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;).  This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.  We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;album-content&#34;&gt;Album Content&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Service transfers your photos, videos, audios, documents, notes, albums, and folder structures (&amp;ldquo;Album Content&amp;rdquo;) between the devices which you login through the 1Album mobile application and/or the 1Album Blackbox application (&amp;ldquo;Personal Devices&amp;rdquo;). We do not monitor, store, maintain, or distribute your Album Content outside of your Personal Devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-collection-and-use&#34;&gt;Information Collection And Use&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, profile picture, and other information (&amp;ldquo;Personal Information&amp;rdquo;). We may obtain your Persional Information through a third party account provider when you sign in to our Service.  We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;log-data&#34;&gt;Log Data&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device (&amp;ldquo;Log Data&amp;rdquo;). This Log Data may include information such as your computer&amp;rsquo;s Internet Protocol (&amp;ldquo;IP&amp;rdquo;) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Log Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use and other statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this type of information in order to increase our Service&amp;rsquo;s functionality. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;cookies&#34;&gt;Cookies&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer&amp;rsquo;s hard drive. We use &amp;ldquo;cookies&amp;rdquo; to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--### DoubleClick Cookie--&gt;

&lt;!--Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google&#39;s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other web sites on the Internet.--&gt;

&lt;!--You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/--&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;service-providers&#34;&gt;Service Providers&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. We do not provide your Album Content to these third parties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;compliance-with-laws&#34;&gt;Compliance With Laws&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement or to protect the security or integrity of our Service. Nevertheless, because we do not store your Album Content in our servers, we cannot and therefore will not disclose your Album Content.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;business-transaction&#34;&gt;Business Transaction&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If 1 Digital Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Information may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Information is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;security&#34;&gt;Security&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;international-transfer&#34;&gt;International Transfer&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your information, including Personal Information, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction. If you are located outside Taiwan and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the information, including Personal Information, to Taiwan and process it there.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We do not transfer your Album Content to our computers in Taiwan.  Your Album Content is transferred between — and maintained on — your Personal Devices. If you put your Personal Devices outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction, please note that we transfer your Album Content to where your Personal Devices are located.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;links-to-other-sites&#34;&gt;Links To Other Sites&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party&amp;rsquo;s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;children-s-privacy&#34;&gt;Children&amp;rsquo;s Privacy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (&amp;ldquo;Children&amp;rdquo;). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Information from a children under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;changes-to-this-privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Changes To This Privacy Policy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:service@1album.net&#34;&gt;service@1album.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1 Digital Inc.&lt;br&gt;
4F-1, No.48, Sec.2, Keelung Rd., Taipei 110, Taiwan&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 class=&#34;pull-right&#34;&gt;Last updated: June 15, 2016&lt;/h5&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://1album.net/tw/support/foss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1album.net/tw/support/foss/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;style&gt;a { overflow-wrap: break-word; word-wrap: break-word; } &lt;/style&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;1album-內第三方軟體&#34;&gt;1Album 內第三方軟體&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1 Digital Inc. (&amp;ldquo;us&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;) includes computer software supplied by third-parties, including (but not limited to) those set forth below (the “Third-Party Software”), with the 1Album mobile application and the 1Album Blackbox application (&amp;ldquo;1Album Software&amp;rdquo;). We are providing the Third-Party Software to you by permission of the respective licensors and/or copyright holders on the terms provided by such parties, including those terms required to be provided to you that are set forth below, and subject also to the End User License Agreement applicable to the 1Album Software. Without limiting the terms in the End User License Agreement, we expressly disclaims any warranty or other assurance to you regarding the Third-Party Software. The following terms relate only to the Third-Party Software identified below and not to the 1Album Software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;boost-c-libraries-boost&#34;&gt;Boost C++ Libraries - boost&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://boost.org/&#34;&gt;http://boost.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boost Software License - Version 1.0 - August 17th, 2003&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person or organization obtaining a copy of the software and accompanying documentation covered by this license (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;) to use, reproduce, display, distribute, execute, and transmit the Software, and to prepare derivative works of the Software, and to permit third-parties to whom the Software is furnished to do so, all subject to the following:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The copyright notices in the Software and this entire statement, including the above license grant, this restriction and the following disclaimer, must be included in all copies of the Software, in whole or in part, and all derivative works of the Software, unless such copies or derivative works are solely in the form of machine-executable object code generated by a source language processor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS OR ANYONE DISTRIBUTING THE SOFTWARE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;json-for-modern-c&#34;&gt;JSON for Modern C++&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nlohmann/json&#34;&gt;https://github.com/nlohmann/json&lt;/a&gt;
Licensed under the MIT license&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2013-2016 &lt;a href=&#34;http://nlohmann.me/&#34;&gt;Niels Lohmann&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;opencv&#34;&gt;OpenCV&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://opencv.org/&#34;&gt;http://opencv.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;License Agreement For Open Source Computer Vision Library (3-clause BSD License)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither the names of the copyright holders nor the names of the contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software without specific prior written permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This software is provided by the copyright holders and contributors “as is” and any express or implied warranties, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose are disclaimed. In no event shall copyright holders or contributors be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, or consequential damages (including, but not limited to, procurement of substitute goods or services; loss of use, data, or profits; or business interruption) however caused and on any theory of liability, whether in contract, strict liability, or tort (including negligence or otherwise) arising in any way out of the use of this software, even if advised of the possibility of such damage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;openssl&#34;&gt;OpenSSL&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.openssl.org/&#34;&gt;http://www.openssl.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 1998-2016 The OpenSSL Project.  All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
 modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
 are met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;All advertising materials mentioning features or use of this
software must display the following acknowledgment:
&amp;ldquo;This product includes software developed by the OpenSSL Project
for use in the OpenSSL Toolkit. (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.openssl.org/)&amp;quot;&#34;&gt;http://www.openssl.org/)&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The names &amp;ldquo;OpenSSL Toolkit&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;OpenSSL Project&amp;rdquo; must not be used to
endorse or promote products derived from this software without
prior written permission. For written permission, please contact
openssl-core@openssl.org.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Products derived from this software may not be called &amp;ldquo;OpenSSL&amp;rdquo;
nor may &amp;ldquo;OpenSSL&amp;rdquo; appear in their names without prior written
permission of the OpenSSL Project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions of any form whatsoever must retain the following
acknowledgment:
&amp;ldquo;This product includes software developed by the OpenSSL Project
for use in the OpenSSL Toolkit (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.openssl.org/)&amp;quot;&#34;&gt;http://www.openssl.org/)&amp;quot;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE OpenSSL PROJECT ``AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND ANY
 EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
 IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
 PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE OpenSSL PROJECT OR
 ITS CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
 SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
 NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
 LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
 HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
 STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)
 ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED
 OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;protocol-buffers&#34;&gt;Protocol Buffers&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google/protobuf&#34;&gt;https://github.com/google/protobuf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright 2014, Google Inc.  All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer
in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither the name of Google Inc. nor the names of its
contributors may be used to endorse or promote products derived from
this software without specific prior written permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Code generated by the Protocol Buffer compiler is owned by the owner
of the input file used when generating it.  This code is not
standalone and requires a support library to be linked with it.  This
support library is itself covered by the above license.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;socket-io-c-client&#34;&gt;Socket.IO C++ Client&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/socketio/socket.io-client-cpp&#34;&gt;https://github.com/socketio/socket.io-client-cpp&lt;/a&gt;
Licensed under the MIT license&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2015, Melo Yao. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to all conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;spdlog&#34;&gt;spdlog&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gabime/spdlog/&#34;&gt;https://github.com/gabime/spdlog/&lt;/a&gt;
Licensed under the MIT license&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2016 Gabi Melman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;sqlite3&#34;&gt;sqlite3&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.sqlite.org/index.html&#34;&gt;http://www.sqlite.org/index.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the code and documentation in SQLite has been dedicated to the public domain  by the authors. All code authors, and representatives of the companies they work for, have signed affidavits dedicating their contributions to the public domain and originals of those signed affidavits are stored in a firesafe at the main offices of Hwaci . Anyone is free to copy, modify, publish, use, compile, sell, or distribute the original SQLite code, either in source code form or as a compiled binary, for any purpose, commercial or non-commercial, and by any means.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The previous paragraph applies to the deliverable code and documentation in SQLite - those parts of the SQLite library that you actually bundle and ship with a larger application. Some scripts used as part of the build process (for example the &amp;ldquo;configure&amp;rdquo; scripts generated by autoconf) might fall under other open-source licenses. Nothing from these build scripts ever reaches the final deliverable SQLite library, however, and so the licenses associated with those scripts should not be a factor in assessing your rights to copy and use the SQLite library.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of the deliverable code in SQLite has been written from scratch. No code has been taken from other projects or from the open internet. Every line of code can be traced back to its original author, and all of those authors have public domain dedications on file. So the SQLite code base is clean and is uncontaminated with licensed code from other projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;sqlite3pp&#34;&gt;sqlite3pp&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/iwongu/sqlite3pp/&#34;&gt;https://github.com/iwongu/sqlite3pp/&lt;/a&gt;
Licensed under the MIT license&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2015 Wongoo Lee (iwongu at gmail dot com)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.  IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;webrtc-software-license&#34;&gt;WebRTC Software License&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://webrtc.org&#34;&gt;https://webrtc.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2011, The WebRTC project authors. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
the documentation and/or other materials provided with the
distribution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither the name of Google nor the names of its contributors may
be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
without specific prior written permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR
A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT
HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL,
SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT
LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE,
DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY
THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE
OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;websocket&#34;&gt;WebSocket++&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zaphoyd/websocketpp&#34;&gt;https://github.com/zaphoyd/websocketpp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2014, Peter Thorson. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither the name of the WebSocket++ Project nor the
names of its contributors may be used to endorse or promote products
derived from this software without specific prior written permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;
AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL PETER THORSON BE LIABLE FOR ANY
DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES;
LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND
ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS
SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Cocoapods --&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;facebook-ios-sdk&#34;&gt;Facebook iOS SDK&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://developers.facebook.com/docs/ios/&#34;&gt;https://developers.facebook.com/docs/ios/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2014-present, Facebook, Inc. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are hereby granted a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free license to use,
copy, modify, and distribute this software in source code or binary form for use
in connection with the web services and APIs provided by Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with any software that integrates with the Facebook platform, your use of
this software is subject to the Facebook Developer Principles and Policies
[&lt;a href=&#34;http://developers.facebook.com/policy/&#34;&gt;http://developers.facebook.com/policy/&lt;/a&gt;]. This copyright notice shall be
included in all copies or substantial portions of the software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS
FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR
COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER
IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN
CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;datetools&#34;&gt;DateTools&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/MatthewYork/DateTools&#34;&gt;https://github.com/MatthewYork/DateTools&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2014 Matthew York.
Licensed under the MIT license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&#34;&gt;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;fontawesomekit&#34;&gt;FontAwesomeKit&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/PrideChung/FontAwesomeKit&#34;&gt;https://github.com/PrideChung/FontAwesomeKit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Licensed under the MIT license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&#34;&gt;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;mbprogresshud&#34;&gt;MBProgressHUD&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jdg/MBProgressHUD&#34;&gt;https://github.com/jdg/MBProgressHUD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Licensed under the MIT license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&#34;&gt;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;mgswipetablecell&#34;&gt;MGSwipeTableCell&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/MortimerGoro/MGSwipeTableCell&#34;&gt;https://github.com/MortimerGoro/MGSwipeTableCell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2014 Imanol Fernandez @MortimerGoro
Licensed under the MIT license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&#34;&gt;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;mrprogress&#34;&gt;MRProgress&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/mrackwitz/MRProgress&#34;&gt;https://github.com/mrackwitz/MRProgress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2013 Marius Rackwitz git@mariusrackwitz.de.
Licensed under the MIT license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&#34;&gt;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;uiimageviewmodescaleaspect&#34;&gt;UIImageViewModeScaleAspect&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/VivienCormier/UIImageViewModeScaleAspect&#34;&gt;https://github.com/VivienCormier/UIImageViewModeScaleAspect&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright &amp;copy; 2013 Vivien Cormier (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.viviencormier.fr/&#34;&gt;http://www.viviencormier.fr/&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--
    Output from GoogleMap SDK: GMSServices.openSourceLicenseInfo()
--&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;google-toolbox-for-mac&#34;&gt;Google Toolbox For Mac:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2006-2013 Google Inc.
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#34;&gt;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&lt;/a&gt;).
Google Toolbox For Mac (&lt;a href=&#34;https://code.google.com/p/google-toolbox-for-mac&#34;&gt;https://code.google.com/p/google-toolbox-for-mac&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;iglu&#34;&gt;iGLU:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;iGLU (&lt;a href=&#34;https://code.google.com/p/iphone-glu/&#34;&gt;https://code.google.com/p/iphone-glu/&lt;/a&gt;) is an implementation of the OpenGL Utility Library (GLU) (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.opengl.org/documentation/specs/&#34;&gt;http://www.opengl.org/documentation/specs/&lt;/a&gt;) for iPhone OS (&lt;a href=&#34;http://developer.apple.com/iphone/&#34;&gt;http://developer.apple.com/iphone/&lt;/a&gt;). iGLU is based on the GLU source included with Mesa 7.2 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://mesa3d.sourceforge.net/&#34;&gt;http://mesa3d.sourceforge.net/&lt;/a&gt;), which in turn derives from the SGI OpenGL Sample Implementation (&lt;a href=&#34;http://oss.sgi.com/projects/ogl-sample/&#34;&gt;http://oss.sgi.com/projects/ogl-sample/&lt;/a&gt;). All code derived from SGI&amp;rsquo;s source is licensed under the SGI Free Software License B version 2.0 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://oss.sgi.com/projects/FreeB/&#34;&gt;http://oss.sgi.com/projects/FreeB/&lt;/a&gt;). All other code is licensed under the MIT license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&#34;&gt;http://www.opensource.org/licenses/mit-license.php&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;nimbus&#34;&gt;Nimbus:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2011-2012 Jeff Verkoeyen
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#34;&gt;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&lt;/a&gt;).
NimbusKit.info (&lt;a href=&#34;http://NimbusKit.info&#34;&gt;http://NimbusKit.info&lt;/a&gt;) - List of contributors (&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jverkoey/nimbus/graphs/contributors&#34;&gt;https://github.com/jverkoey/nimbus/graphs/contributors&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;material-components-for-ios&#34;&gt;Material Components for iOS:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2015-2016 Google, Inc.
Licensed under the Apache license, Version 2.0 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#34;&gt;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;objective-c-protocol-buffers&#34;&gt;Objective C Protocol Buffers:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2008 Cyrus Najmabadi.
Copyright © 2010 Booyah Inc.
Copyright © 2011-2013 Google Inc.
Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#34;&gt;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&lt;/a&gt;).
Objective C Protocol Buffers (&lt;a href=&#34;https://code.google.com/p/metasyntactic/wiki/ProtocolBuffers&#34;&gt;https://code.google.com/p/metasyntactic/wiki/ProtocolBuffers&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;zlib&#34;&gt;zlib:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 1995-2013 Jean-loup Gailly and Mark Adler
Licensed under the zlib license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://zlib.net/zlib_license.html&#34;&gt;http://zlib.net/zlib_license.html&lt;/a&gt;).
zlib (&lt;a href=&#34;http://zlib.net/&#34;&gt;http://zlib.net/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;jquery-easing&#34;&gt;JQuery Easing:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2008 George McGinley Smith.
Copyright © 2001 Robert Penner All rights reserved.
Licensed under the BSD license (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.robertpenner.com/easing_terms_of_use.html&#34;&gt;http://www.robertpenner.com/easing_terms_of_use.html&lt;/a&gt;).
jQuery Easing Plugin (&lt;a href=&#34;http://gsgd.co.uk/sandbox/jquery/easing/&#34;&gt;http://gsgd.co.uk/sandbox/jquery/easing/&lt;/a&gt;)
Robert Penner&amp;rsquo;s Easing Functions (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.robertpenner.com/easing/&#34;&gt;http://www.robertpenner.com/easing/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;font-siemreap&#34;&gt;font &amp;lsquo;Siemreap&amp;rsquo;:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2010 Danh Hong (khmertype.blogspot.com).
Licensed under the SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://scripts.sil.org/OFL&#34;&gt;http://scripts.sil.org/OFL&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;font-tharlon-regular&#34;&gt;font &amp;lsquo;Tharlon-Regular&amp;rsquo;:&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2012, Sun Tun, Ngwe Tun, Solveware Solution (&lt;a href=&#34;http://code.google.com/p/tharlon-font&#34;&gt;http://code.google.com/p/tharlon-font&lt;/a&gt;).
Based on the font &amp;lsquo;Yunghkio&amp;rsquo; : Copyright © 2010-2012, Sai Zin Di Di Zone (&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yunghkio.com/unicode&#34;&gt;http://www.yunghkio.com/unicode&lt;/a&gt;)
and the font &amp;lsquo;Arimo&amp;rsquo;: Copyright © 2012, Google, Inc (&lt;a href=&#34;http://code.google.com/p/googlefontdirectory/&#34;&gt;http://code.google.com/p/googlefontdirectory/&lt;/a&gt;)
Licensed under the SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://scripts.sil.org/OFL&#34;&gt;http://scripts.sil.org/OFL&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- fonts used by FontAwesomeKit --&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;font-font-awesome&#34;&gt;font &amp;lsquo;Font Awesome&amp;rsquo;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://fontawesome.io&#34;&gt;http://fontawesome.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Licensed under the SIL Open Font License, Version 1.1 (&lt;a href=&#34;http://scripts.sil.org/OFL&#34;&gt;http://scripts.sil.org/OFL&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;icons-icons8&#34;&gt;icons &amp;lsquo;Icons8&amp;rsquo;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://icons8.com&#34;&gt;https://icons8.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Licensed under Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported, Version 3.0 (&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/3.0/&#34;&gt;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nd/3.0/&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>